https://www.alford.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Privacy Policy
At The Alford Group we respect and protect the privacy of our customers and those who use our website. The following Privacy Statement provides details about how your personal information is collected and used.
Information Collection and Use
The Alford Group is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. The Alford Group collects information from our users at several different points on our website.
Our website offers several opportunities for visitors to contact us. These “contact” forms are often linked to our mailing list and require users to give contact information such as name and email address. We use this contact information to send users information about our company.
Sharing and Usage
We will never share, sell, or rent your personal information with third parties for their promotional use.
Links
Our site provides links to third-party websites. While on these sites, The Alford Group or its partners may collect information about you. Because The Alford Group does not control the information policies or practices of these third parties, you should review their privacy policies to learn more about how they collect and use personally identifiable information.
Notification of Changes
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on www.alford.com so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.
Share:Click to share on Facebook (Opens in new window)Click to share on LinkedIn (Opens in new window)Click to share on Twitter (Opens in new window)
Are you on track? Maybe an outside perspective is just what you need.
